A Guide to the Executive journal indexes of the Secretary of the Commonwealth,, 1832-1981
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Executive journal indexes of the Secretary of the Commonwealth,, 1832-1981
The Library of Virginia
35185
6.7 cu. ft. (67 volumes)
Virginia. Secretary of the Commonwealth.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on
Biographical Information
Beginning in 1832, the secretary of the commonwealth began keeping an executive journal recording correspondence received by the governor and actions taken by him. This system of record-keeping continued until 1866. Record-keeping for the governors changed in 1866. The secretary of the commonwealth filed records related to official action taken by the governor, such as appointments, resignations, pardon requests, and executive orders.
Scope and Content
These volumes provide a chronological listing of the Governor's activities regarding appointments, executive orders and memorandums, commissions, notaries, pardons, proclamations, writs of election, restorations of rights, renditions and requisitions as recorded by the Secretary of the Commonwealth.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Executive journal indexes, 1832 March 16-1833 March 30 (Box 1)
- Executive journal indexes, 1833 April-1834 March (Box 2)
- Executive journal indexes, 1834 March 31-1835 September 24 (Box 3)
- Executive journal indexes, 1835 October 2-1837 March 30 (Box 4)
- Executive journal indexes, 1837 March-1838 October (Box 5)
- Executive journal indexes, 1838 November 2-1840 March 30 (Box 6)
- Executive journal indexes, 1840 March-1842 March (Box 7)
- Executive journal indexes, 1842 March 31-1845 December (Box 8)
- Executive journal indexes, 1845 December 22-1847 August (Box 9)
- Executive journal indexes, 1847 September-1848 December (Box 10)
- Executive journal indexes, 1849 January-1850 December (Box 11)
- Executive journal indexes, 1851 (Box 12)
- Executive journal indexes, 1852 (Box 13)
- Executive journal indexes, 1853 (Box 14)
- Executive journal indexes, 1854 (Box 15)
- Executive journal indexes, 1855 (Box 16)
- Executive journal indexes, 1856 (Box 17)
- Executive journal indexes, 1857 (Box 18)
- Executive journal indexes, 1858 (Box 19)
- Executive journal indexes, 1859 (Box 20)
- Executive journal indexes, 1860 (Box 21)
- Executive journal indexes, 1861 (Box 22)
- Executive journal indexes, 1862 January-1863 October (Box 23)
- Executive journal indexes, 1863 November-1865 April (Box 24)
- Executive journal indexes, 1864 May 11-1867 December (Box 25)
- Executive journal indexes, 1868 (Box 26)
- Executive journal indexes, 1870 (Box 27)
- Executive journal indexes, 1871 (Box 28)
- Executive journal indexes, 1872 (Box 29)
- Executive journal indexes, 1873 (Box 30)
- Executive journal indexes, 1874 (Box 31)
- Executive journal indexes, 1875 (Box 32)
- Executive journal indexes, 1876 (Box 33)
- Executive journal indexes, 1877 (Box 34)
- Executive journal indexes, 1878 (Box 35)
- Executive journal indexes, 1879 (Box 36)
- Executive journal indexes, 1880 (Box 37)
- Executive journal indexes, 1881 (Box 38)
- Executive journal indexes, 1882 (Box 39)
- Executive journal indexes, 1883 (Box 40)
- Executive journal indexes, 1884-1885 (Box 41)
- Executive journal indexes, 1886-1888 (Box 42)
- Executive journal indexes, 1889 (Box 43)
- Executive journal indexes, 1890-1893 (Box 44)
- Executive journal indexes, 1894 January-1896 October (Box 45)
- Executive journal indexes, 1896 November 2-1899 December (Box 46)
- Executive journal indexes, 1900-1901 (Box 47)
- Executive journal indexes, 1902 January 2-1906 January 31 (Box 48)
- Executive journal indexes, 1906 February 1-1910 January 31 (Box 49)
- Executive journal indexes, 1910 February-1914 February (Box 50)
- Executive journal indexes, 1914-1918 (Box 51)
- Executive journal indexes, 1918-1922 (Box 52)
- Executive journal indexes, 1922-1926 (Box 53)
- Executive journal indexes, 1926 February-1930 January (Box 54)
- Executive journal indexes, 1930 January-1934 January (Box 55)
- Executive journal indexes, 1924 January-1938 January (Box 56)
- Executive journal indexes, 1938 January 18-1942 January 20 (Box 57)
- Executive journal indexes, 1942 January 21-1946 January 15 (Box 58)
- Executive journal indexes, 1946-1950 (Box 59)
- Executive journal indexes, 1950-1954 (Box 60)
- Executive journal indexes, 1954-1958 (Box 61)
- Executive journal indexes, 1958-1962 (Box 62)
- Executive journal indexes, 1962-1966 (Box 63)
- Executive journal indexes, 1966-1970 (Box 64)
- Executive journal indexes, 1970-1974 (Box 65)
- Executive journal indexes, 1974-1978 (Box 66)
- Executive journal indexes, 1979-1981 (Box 67)